<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>


<videos>

    <details>
        <title>The Silent Gun</title>
        <airDate>September 09, 1966</airDate>
        <videoLength>RunTime: 24:07</videoLength>
        <description>In this premiere episode, Dave Bannister is shot at a funeral with 20
        witnesses present and not a shot was heard, not even from the Green Hornet's
        friend, the District Attorney, who was also attending. A messenger from a Brokerage House,
        carrying $5000 in negotiable bonds, is the Silent Gun's second victim. The Green Hornet
        and Kato respond in the infamous Black Beauty and hit the streets to track down the villainous
        culprit.</description>
    </details>

    <details>
        <title>Give'em Enough Rope </title>
        <airDate>September 16, 1966</airDate>
        <videoLength>RunTime: 24:46</videoLength>
        <description>In this premiere episode, Dave Bannister is shot at a funeral with 20 witnesses present and not a
        shot was heard, not even from the Green Hornet's friend, the District Attorney, who was also
        attending. A messenger from a Brokerage House, carrying $5000 in negotiable bonds, is the Silent
        Gun's second victim. The Green Hornet and Kato respond in the infamous Black Beauty and hit the
        streets to track down the villainous culprit. </description>
    </details>

    <details>
        <title>Programmed For Death </title>
        <airDate>September 23, 1966</airDate>
        <videoLength>RunTime: 24:45</videoLength>
        <description>After reporter Pat Allen, is killed in the Daily Sentinel 's eighth floor city room by a leopard,
        Britt Reid finds a transmitter in a cigarette box. Later, D.A. Scanlon informs Britt of the
        discovery of a perfect diamond on Allen's desk. Digging around, Reid suspects that the gemologist
        had been working on producing synthetic diamonds, and the Green Hornet takes an interest in him.
        </description>
    </details>
</videos>